<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Andrew's Musings]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.andrewenfield.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.andrewenfield.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-08-15T14:54:17-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.andrewenfield.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Andrew Enfield]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[New code, new machine]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.andrewenfield.com/blog/2014/08/15/new-code/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-15T14:45:13-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.andrewenfield.com/blog/2014/08/15/new-code</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If this text is public, it means I&rsquo;ve successfully rebooted my previously-rebooted blog. Specifically, it means this post has been generated from Markdown written using TextMate on a Mac, has had its HTML generated by an updated version of <a href="http://octopress.org">Octopress</a> running with Ruby and rbenv on a Mac instead of Windows (based on a manually-added Git remote I used to merge the latest Octopress source with what I had from two years ago), and is being deployed on Heroku using a new Heroku app with the Cedar stack.</p>

<p>Cool.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Press restart]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.andrewenfield.com/blog/2012/06/10/press-restart/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-10T20:13:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.andrewenfield.com/blog/2012/06/10/press-restart</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I had a blog in 2003 and 2004. I started it because I happened upon a blog engine written using ASP.NET (<a href="http://dasblog.codeplex.com">http://dasblog.codeplex.com</a>), and I thought it&rsquo;d be cool to see how the engine worked under the covers. I posted occasionally at <a href="http://enfieldfamily.com">http://enfieldfamily.com</a>. The most popular post was, I think, a &ldquo;here&rsquo;s how you fix&rdquo; something entry - I can&rsquo;t remember for what - that came up first or second in searches. When I changed jobs toward the end of 2004 I started doing work that wasn&rsquo;t going to generate posts, and the blog went dead.</p>

<p>Now, eight years later, I&rsquo;ve <a href="http://www.peterprovost.org/blog/2012/04/15/switching-the-blog-to-octopress/">read about another blog engine</a> that looks interesting, in part because the guts are visible (<a href="http://octopress.org">http://octopress.org</a>). My job is also now such that I may have things worth writing down. So I&rsquo;ll try it again.</p>

<p>Some possible upcoming posts: credit where credit&rsquo;s due for Octopress, which is pretty cool; info from the trenches about MSBuild, TFS, and ClickOnce projects.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
